solopress.com 2017-06-06

# Our Privacy Policy - Solopress

* * *

## Privacy Policy

* * *

This privacy policy was last revised on 23 February 2017.

**About Us and this Privacy Policy**

The website at [www.solopress.com](http://www.solopress.com/), is owned and operated by AGA Print Limited. We are registered in England under company number 04717223 and our registered office is at 9 Stock Road, Southend On Sea, Essex, SS2 5QF. For the purposes of the Data Protection Act 1998, we are the data controller. We are registered as a data controller with the Information Commissioner's Office under registration number ZA148062.

This privacy policy has been prepared to meet the requirements of the UK's Data Protection Act 1998 and The Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) Regulations 2003. It intended to help you understand our practices relating to the collection, protection, disclosure and use of any personal data that you provide to us, or that we collect from you, whilst you visit our site. By "personal data", we mean any information about you that could be used to help identify you. Nothing in this privacy policy limits your legal rights in relation to your personal data.

By providing your personal data to us, you agree that we may collect and use the personal data you provide in the ways described in this privacy policy. Please read each of the following sections carefully to understand our views and practices. If you do not agree with the terms of this privacy policy, please do not provide any personal data to us.

Please note that we may need to update this privacy policy from time to time to reflect changes in our practices and the law. We recommend that you check this page regularly to ensure that you have read the most recent version and that you are happy with any changes.

**Information We Collect**

We may collect and process the following personal data about you:

i.        Information about your use of our site including details of your visits such as pages viewed and the resources that you access. Such information includes traffic data, location data and other communication data.

ii.      Information provided voluntarily by you. For example, when you create an account or make a purchase, you may provide your name, address, email address, telephone number and company name.

iii.     Information that you provide when you communicate with us by any means, including when you engage in a "Live Chat" on our site, respond to our marketing communications, enter our competitions, complete our voluntary surveys or report a problem with our site.

iv.     Your email address when you subscribe to receive information about Solopress news, offers and competitions.

**Use of Cookies**

Our site uses cookies to distinguish you from other visitors. This helps us to provide you with a more personalised experience when you browse the site and also allows us to improve our site. For detailed information on the cookies we use and the purposes for which we use them, please take a look at our _cookie policy._

**Use of Your Information**

We use the information that we collect from you for one or more of the following purposes:

i.        To provide the products and services you order from us and to carry out our obligations and exercise our rights arising from those orders.

ii.      To provide information to you that you request from us relating to our products or services. 

iii.     To inform you of any changes to our site and/or our products and services.

iv.     To administer our site and for internal operations, including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, research, statistical and survey purposes.

v.       To ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer.

vi.     To provide you with information about products and services we offer that we feel may interest you by post, telephone, email and/or SMS. We will send that information by electronic mail (including email and/or SMS) only if: (i) you have consented to this, for example by opting in at the time you create an account, place an order or complete the email subscription form on our site; or (ii) the information is about our products and services similar to those which were the subject of a previous sale or negotiation of a sale to you and you have not opted out of receiving such marketing messages; or (iii) where we are permitted to do so by law without consent, for example, if you have provided us with a company email address. If you do not want us to use your personal data in this way, please let us know using our contact details at the end of this privacy policy.

vii.    If you have a Facebook account, we may provide you with information about our products and services through Facebook, using Facebook's "Custom Audience" feature. This feature allows us to ensure that you are receiving advertising from us that is most appropriate to you. To do this, we send your email address to Facebook in "hashed" form, which means we convert it into a string of numbers that cannot be reversed to reveal your email address. When Facebook receives the hashed data, it matches it against its own list of hashed data and if it has a hash which corresponds to your email address it will present our advertisement to you. Learn more about Custom Audiences at <https://en-gb.facebook.com/business/help/341425252616329>. If you do not wish to receive information about our products and services through Facebook, you can opt out at any time by contacting us using our details at the end of this privacy policy.  

**Storing Your Personal Data**

We will only retain and use your personal information for as long as we need it for the purposes set out in this privacy policy or as otherwise required by law.

All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers. We have in place a level of security appropriate to the nature of the information stored and the harm that might result from a breach of security.

Unfortunately the sending of information via the internet is not totally secure and on occasion such information can be intercepted. We cannot guarantee the security of data that you choose to send us electronically and therefore sending such information is entirely at your own risk.

The information that we collect from you may be transferred to a destination outside the European Economic Area (" **EEA** "), where it will be stored by us or by one of our suppliers. It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers. Such suppliers and staff may be engaged in, among other things, the provision of support services. We will take reasonable steps to ensure adequate security for any of your information transferred outside the EEA, but please be aware that destinations outside the EEA to which your information may be transferred may have data protection laws which do not offer the same level of protection for your information as those in force in the EEA. By using our site and submitting your information to us, you agree to the transfer, storing and processing of such information outside the EEA as set out in this privacy policy. By using the website and submitting your personal information, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing of such personal information outside the EEA as set out in this privacy policy

**Payments on our Site**

All payments on our site are processed by PayPal or Sage Pay. When you make a payment on our site, you are providing your payment details to the relevant third-party payment processor, and not to us. We do not receive and therefore do not store any of your payment details when you make an online payment. PayPal and Sage Pay process your payment details for the purpose of processing your online payment for our products and services. PayPal's privacy policy can be found here: [www.paypal.com/uk/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full](http://www.paypal.com/uk/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full). Sage Pay's privacy policy can be found here: www.sagepay.co.uk/policies.

**Disclosing Your Information**

We may share your personal data with any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries, as defined in section 1159 of the UK Companies Act 2006 (" **Group** "). For the avoidance of doubt, we may disclose your personal information to ASAP Print Limited

We will not disclose your personal information to any other party other than in accordance with this privacy policy and in the circumstances detailed below:

i.        We may disclose your personal data to our sub-contractors and other suppliers and service providers who we engage to assist with our administrative or business functions and to deal with any other matters in connection with our site, our products and services and any agreements we enter into with you.

ii.      We may disclose your personal data to credit reference agencies for the purpose of assessing your creditworthiness where this is a condition of us entering into an agreement with you.

iii.     We may disclose your personal data to analytics and search engine providers that assist us in the improvement and optimisation of our site.

iv.     We may disclose your personal data to advertisers and advertising networks that require anonymised data to select and serve relevant adverts to you and others. We may provide them with aggregate information about our users (for example, we may inform them that 100 women aged 18-30 have clicked on their advertisement on any given day). We may also use such aggregate information to help advertisers reach the kind of audience they want to target (for example, men in a particular location). We may make use of the information we have collected from you to enable us to comply with our advertisers' wishes by displaying their advertisement to that target audience.  

v.       In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer.

vi.     If AGA Print Limited or any member of the Group, or substantially all of its or their assets, are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its or their customers may be one of the transferred assets.

vii.    If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our _Terms and Conditions_ and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of AGA Print Limited or any member of the Group or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

**Third Party Links**

This privacy policy only covers this site. On occasion we include links to third parties on our site. Where we provide a link it does not mean that we endorse or approve that site's policy towards visitor privacy. You should review their privacy policy and consider their reputation before sending them any personal data.

**Opting Out of Marketing**

You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. If you would like to do so, just let us know using our contact details at the end of this privacy policy. However, if you exercise your right to opt-out of receiving marketing messages from us, please be aware that you may continue to receive certain non-marketing communications from us. For example, we may still need to contact you about important changes to our products, services or site that affect you or about any agreements we may have entered into with you.

**Access to Information**

In accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998 you have the right to access any personal data that we hold relating to you. Please note that we reserve the right to charge a fee of GBP 10.00 to cover costs incurred by us in providing you with the information. If you would like a copy of this information, please write to us at the address below.

**Contacting Us**

Please do not hesitate to contact us regarding any matter relating to this privacy policy. Questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed and should be sent to us by email at [info@solopress.com](mailto:info@solopress.com) or by post to 9 Stock Road, Southend-on-Sea Essex, SS2 5QF. You are also welcome to call us on 01702 460047.
